Guide to the Richard Kostelanetz Collection 1961-1997 MSS.089
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Articles By Kostelanetz
  - John Cage and Richard Kostelanetz: A Conversation about Radio. The Musical Quarterly. 72:2 -1986 216-27. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - John Cage on Pedagogy. Social Anarchism. 14 -1989 13-29. (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Joseph Brodsky: The Myth of the Privileged Background. Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review. (Feb. -Mar. 1997) 33-4. (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Language and Structure. New York Arts Journal. 1: 2 -1975 13-14. (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Leslie Fielder. Studies in the Twentieth Century. 13 (Spring 1974) 21-38. Offprint. (Box 2, Folder 50a)
  - The Literature of SoHo. Shantih. 4:3-4. (1982) 14-15. (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Literary Video. Visible Language. 29:2 -1995 198-203. (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Literary Video. Pinch Penny. (1982) 14-15. (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - The Literature Professors' Literature Professor. Michigan Quarterly Review. 17: 4 -1978 424-42. (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Major Innovations. Passagesnorth. (Winter 1991) 15-22.; Removed from journal (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Me and AIDS Journalism. Liberty. 4:2 (May-Jun. 1993) 5-6. (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - The Media and Urban Riots. The Kithara. 2:3 (Summer 1994) 7 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Metamorphosis in Modern Dance. Dance Scope. 5:1 -1970 6-21. (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Modern Music Criticism and the Literate Layman. Perspectives of New Music. 6:1 (Fall-Winter 1967) 119-134. Offprint. (Box 2, Folder 58a)
  - My Non-Sync, Two-Person Films (1988). Confrontation. 39-40 -1989 249-55., 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - A Mystic's Music: Arvo Part's Quiet Revolution. Connoisseur. (April 1990) 66-76. (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Item removed to Oversize - look in Box 10 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - New York in Fiction. The Columbia University Forum. 9:3 -1966 44-50. (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - A Note on John Cage and Homosexuality. Sa. IV:2 -1994 5-7. (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Notes on America's Game. Northwest Review. XXVI:2 -1988 128-32. (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Notes on the American Short Story Today. Die amerikanische Short Story. Darmstadt: Wissenshaftliche Buchgesellschaft, 1972. 355-67. (Box 2, Folder 64a)
  - Notes on Composing Kaddish, 1983-1990. News of Music. 12 (Spring 1991) 23-28., 1983-1991 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Nouvelle Poesie Americaine. Art Press International. (Avril 1979) 13-15. (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Il Nuovo Teatro Americano. Nuova Presenza. 15-16 (1964-65) 20-61., 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Off-Broadway Talent. Encore. 2:6 -1964 31-41. (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - On Irving Howe. Salmagundi. 2:1 -1967 44-60. (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - The Persistence of the Avant-Garde: An Interview with Richard Kostelanetz. Cultural Information Service. (February 1973) 2-7. (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Poetry in America. Writer's Digest. (December 1975): [1], 15-21. (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - The Politics of Unresolved Quests in the Novels of Richard Wright. Xavier University Studies. (Spring 1970) 31-64. (Box 2, Folder 71a)
  - Profile of Merce Cunningham. Michigan Quarterly Review. 14:4 -1975 363-82. (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - The Radical Gertrude Stein. Midstream. 42:5 -1996 37-38. (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - The Reinventor of English: Gertrude Stein. Forms of the American Imagination: Beitrage zur neueren amerikanischen Literatur. [Innsbrucker Beitrage zur Kulturwissenschaft. Sonderheft 44] Innsbruck: AMOE, 1979. 85-98. (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - The Republic of Letters by Grant Webster. Re Dact 1 -1984 101-2. (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Scene and Not Heard. Harper's Bazaar. 3073 -1967 52, 71, 75, 84. (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Signs of Academia: The Example of Paul de Man. Another Chicago Magazine. 25 -1993 197-202. (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Sleight of Hand, Or How an NEA Fellowship to Me was Reduced and Nearly Killed. Culturefront. 4:2 -1995 51-6. (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Social Philosophy in America, 1945-1965. Western Humanities Review. 31:3 -1977 193-205. (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - The Space of Men. The Urban Review. 2:3 -1967 4, 28. (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Subversion at the NEH? Chronicles of Culture. 9:1 -1985 4-5. (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Talking about Writings through Finnegans Wake. TriQuarterly. 54 -1982 208-16. (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Text-Sound Art: A Survey. Performing Arts Journal. 2:2 -1977 61-70. (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - The Theater of Mixed Means. Cultural Affairs. 2 -1968 28-34. (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Thoughts on Criticism. Panache. 2 -1968 44-50. (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Thoughts on Innovative Art(ist)s. Northwest Review. XXVIII-3, XXIX-1 (1990-1991) 56-60. (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - The Transcendental Contemporary: Profile of Alan Hovhaness. Michigan Quarterly Review. 18:3 (Summer 1979) 365-378. (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Trends in Criticism: North American Critics Since the Forties. Boston University Journal. 25:2 -1977 59-68. (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Tributes to Henry Ford. Continuum. 2:2 (1969). N. p. (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Item removed to Oversize - look in Box 10 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - A Wide-Angle View and Close-up Portrait of Edwin Land and his Cameras. Lithopinion. 9:1 -1974 48-57. (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Words and Images Artfully Entwined. Art International. 14: 7 -1970 44-56. (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Young Writers in North America. The American Pen. 3:4 (Fall 1971) 1-30. (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Series II: Periodicals with Poems, Reviews, Introductions, or Short Fiction by Richard Kostelanetz
  - Abracadabra 3 (1978). (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Acts the Shelflife. 2 (Summer 1988). (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Aethlon: The Journal of Sport Literature. XIII:2 (Spring 1996). (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - After-Image. 1 (1978). (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Alaska Quarterly Review. 2:1,2 (1983). (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item removed to Oversize - look in Box 10 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Alternative Fiction & Poetry. 5,6., undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - American Book News. (1977). (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - American Book Review. 13:02 (Jun. -Jul. 1991). (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - American Book Review. 13:03 (Aug. -Sept 1991). (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - American Book Review. 14:05 (Dec 1992-Jan. 1993)., 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - American Book Review. 14:06 (Feb. -Mar. 1993). (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - American Book Review. 18:03 (Mar. -Apr. 1997). (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - American Letters and Commentary. 7 -1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Anarchy. 32 (Spring 1992). (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Anarchy. 35 (Winter 1993). (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Ann Arbor Review. 23 (1976). (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Ann Arbor Review. 27 (1977). (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Another Chicago Magazine. 30 (1995). (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Approches. 3 (1968). (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Art-Rite. 14 (1976/77)., 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Artzone. 1:1 (1978). (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Aspect. 72/73 (1977). (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Assembling Magazine: The Unbearables. 5 (Oct. 1996). (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Asthetik und Kommunikation Heft 52, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Asylum. 4:02, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Asylum. 4:04, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Asylum. 6:03, 4 (1991), undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Atelier. 4 (1994). (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Atticus Review. 20 (Spring 1991). (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Atticus Review. 21 (1991). (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Aura. 4:2 (1978). (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Avalanches 1990-95 (1995)., 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 32a)
  - Avalon Rising. (Sept 1993). (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - BS 19 (1984). (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Bakunin. 3:03 (1992). (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Bakunin. 5:02 (Winter 1995). (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Ballet Review. 3:2 (1969): 53-56. (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Benzene. (Autumn 1980). (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Blank Gun Silencer. 6 (1993). (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Blank Tape. 2 (1978). (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Blue Light Red Light. 3 (1990). (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Blur: Boston Literary Review. 5 (Spring 1990). (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Blur: Boston Literary Review. 9 (Fall 1992). (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Book Forum. 6:1 (1982). (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Brilliant Corners. 9 (1978). (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Cabvolt. 5 (Fall 1978). (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - The Cafe Review. 3:9 (1992). (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Caliban. 2 (1987). (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Camera. 23:4 (1978). (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Central Park. 13 (1988). (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Chaminade Literary Review. 8,9 (1991). (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Chelsea. 26 (May 1969). (Box 3, Folder 51a)
  - Chicago Review. 26:3 (1974). (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Chicago Review. 28:2 (1976). (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - City Lights Review. 4 (1990). (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Clown War. 3 (1973). (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Clown War. 13 (1977). (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - CLWN WR.. 37 (1996). (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Cobweb Review. (August 1991). (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Columbia Forum. 11:03 (Fall 1968) (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Columbia Forum. 12:03 (Fall 1969) (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - The Commonweal. 77:16:00 (January 11, 1963) 2 copies (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - The Commonweal. 78:19:00 (August 23, 1963) (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - The Commonweal. 85:01:00 (October 7, 1966) (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - The Commonweal. 85:15:00 (January 20, 1967) (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Compound Eye., undated (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Contact. 4:1 [15] (July 1963). (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Contemporary Poetry. 4:2 (1981). (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Context South. 2:1 (1991). (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - El Coqui. 2 (1978). (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Criss-Cross. 5 (1977). (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Criss-Cross. 11,12 (1981). (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Croton Bug. 2 (Dec. 1992). (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Cultural Information. (Feb 1973). (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Cumberland Journal. 15 (1981). (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Davinci. 4 (1975). (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Delfin. 5 (1985). (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Deja Vu. (1987). (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Disjointed Fictions. (Winter 1981). (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - The Dumb Ox. 4 (1977). (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - E Magazine. 1:2 (1976). (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Everyman. (Summer 1974). (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Experimental Fiction. 6 (1989). (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Experimentelle text. 41,42 (1995). (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Extensions. 3 (1969). (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Exquisite Corpse. 3:11,12 (1985). (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Exquisite Corpse. 6:5-10 (1988). (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Exquisite Corpse. 7:1-5 (1989). (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Exquisite Corpse. 39 (1992). (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Exquisite Corpse. 48 (1994). (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Exquisite Corpse. 59 (1996). (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - The Far Point. 7, 8 (1972-3)., 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - The Fault. 6 (1974). (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Fiction. 10:2 (1991). (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Fiction International. 15:01 (1981). (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Fiction International. 19:01 (Fall 1990). (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Fiction International. 19:02 (Spring 1991). (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - The Fiction Review. 1:3, undated (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - The Fiction Review. 10, undated (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Fishwrap. 1:01 -1990 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Fishwrap. 1:02 -1991 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Flipside. 5:1 (Spring, 1991) (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Foothill Quarterly. 2:2 (1977). (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Format (Spring 1981). (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Friebord: Zeitschrift fur Literatur und Kunst. 84 (Feb. 1993). (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Friebord: Zeitschrift fur Literatur und Kunst. 85 (Mar 1993). (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Further State(s) of the Art. 1:2 (1992). (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Gallery Works Eight. (1991). (Box 4, Folder 106a)
  - Gallimaufry. 7 (Summer 1976). (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Gargoyle. 15,16 (1980). (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Gegenschein Quarterly. 910 (1974). (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Glassworks. 2:2,3 (1977). (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Gnome Baker. 7, 8 (1981). (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - The Greensboro Review. 38 (Summer 1985). (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - HR. 19:3 (Winter 1995). (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Homeplanet News. 36 (1993). (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Hot Water Review (1981). (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Images. 4:1., undated (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - Images. 7:1, undated (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - The Independent. 0:2 (1978). (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Inkstone. Winter/Spring (1983). (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Intent. 3:2,3 (1991). (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Internal Weather. 24 (1976). (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Interstate. 8 (1976). (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Interstate. 11 (1978). (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Interstate. 12 (1979). (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Interstate. 15 (1982). (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Interstate. 16 (1984). (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Intrepid. 36-38 (1978). (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Invisible City. 26-27 (1980). (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Iron. 68 (Nov. 1992-Feb 1993)., 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Le Jardin du Monde. (Summer 1977). (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - The Journal of Musicology. (Summer 1996). (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Journal of Unconventional History. 1:3 (Spring 1990). (Box 5, Folder 131a)
  - Kaspahraster. 5 (Jan. 1993). (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Kaspahraster. 6 (Apr. 1993). (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Kaspahraster. 11(Jul. 1994). (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Kiosk. 9 (1996). (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - The Kithara. 2:3 (Summer 1994). (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Konglomerati. 6:2 (1982). (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Koxja. Premier Issue (1996). (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Laughing Bear. 1 (1976). (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Laughing Bear. 2,3 (1977). (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Laughing Bear. 6 (1977). (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Left Curve. 18 (1994). (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Left Curve. 20 (1996). (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Legionnaire (1984). (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Liberty. 3:05 (May 1990). (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Liberty. 4:04 (Mar. 1991). (Box 5, Folder 145a)
  - Liberty. 5:03 (Jan. 1992). (Box 5, Folder 145b)
  - Liberty. 7:03 (Mar. 1994). (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Liberty. 8:01 (Nov. 1994). (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Liberty. 10:02 (Nov. 1996). (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Liberty. 10:03 (Jan. 1997). (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Lightworks. 20,21 (1990). (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Lilliput Review. 52 (Dec. 1993). (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Lilliput Review. 87 (Apr. 1997). (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Lips. 3 (1982). (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Lips. 4 (1982). (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Lips. 5 (1983). (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Lips. 6 (1983). (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Lips. 9 (1985). (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Literary Magazine Review. 15:4 (1996). (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Look Quick. 9:9 (1981). (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Lost & Found Times. 27, undated (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - The Louisville Review. 21, 22 (Fall 1986/Spring 1987)., 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Maelstrom Review. 7:1-2 (1982). (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Magic Realism. 6 (1992). (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - La Mamelle (Winter 1976). (Box 10, Folder 164)
  - Margins. 28, 29, 30 (1976). (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - The Midwest Quarterly. 37:1 (1995). (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Mississippi Mud. 23, undated (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Mississippi Review. 6:01 (1977). (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Mississippi Review. 9:03 (1981). (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Montana Gothic. 6 (1977). (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Mota. 16 (1978). (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Muse-Pie. 2 (1982). (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - The National Poetry Magazine of the Lower East Side. 7:01 (1992). (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - The National Poetry Magazine of the Lower East Side. 8:01 (1993). (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - The National Poetry Magazine of the Lower East Side. 8:02 (1993). (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - The National Poetry Magazine of the Lower East Side. 8:03 (1993). (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - The National Poetry Magazine of the Lower East Side. 9:01 (1994). (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - The National Poetry Magazine of the Lower East Side. 9:02 (1994). (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Neologisms. 2 (Winter 1997). (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Nerve. 2:2,3 (Fall 1995). (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - New Art Examiner. 17:3 (1989). (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - The New Censorship. 2:11 (1992). (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - New York Arts Journal. 6 (1977). (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - New York Arts Journal. 12 (1978). (Box 10, Folder 183a)
  - Nimrod. 36:1 (1992). (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Northwest Review. 18:02 (1979). (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Northwest Review. 21:00 2, 3, undated (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Northwest Review. 33:01:00 (1995). (Box 6, Folder 187)
  - O. ARS. 1 (1981) (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - O. ARS. 2 (1982). (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - O. ARS. 9 (1993-1994). (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - Object 6 (Jan. 1996). (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - Only Paper Today. 4:9 (1977). (Box 10, Folder 192)
  - The orange police x-ray wedding (winter 95-96)., undated (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Ottotole. 3 (Spring 1989). (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Owen Wister Review. 14:02 (1991). (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Owen Wister Review. (Spring 1993). (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Oyez Review. 6 (1978). (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Oyez Review. 23 (1994). (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - PN Review. 7:3 (1980). (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Panache. 2 (1968). (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Panache. 3 (1969). (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Panache. 15 (1970). (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Panache. Special Issue (1971). (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Panache. 15 (1973). (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Paramour. 4:2 (1997). (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Partisan Review. 49:1 (1982). (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Passages North. 12:2 (Winter 1991). (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Pembroke Magazine. 20 (1988). (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Pembroke Magazine. 25 (1993). (Box 6, Folder 208a)
  - Perspectives of New Music (Spring-Summer 1986). (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Phoebus 2:01 (1984). (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Pikeville Review (1995). (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Poetry Australia. 59 (1976). (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - Poetry East. 25 (1988). (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - Poets On. 2:01 (1978). (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - Poets On. 5:01 (1981). (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Poet's Sanctuary. 5 (Mar. 1994). (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Pop-Cult. 1:3 (Winter 1992). (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Portable Wall. 22 (1993). (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Portable Wall. 23 (1994). (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Portland Review. 27:1 (1981). (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Precisely. 1 (1977). (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Primer. 3 (1977). (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - The Progressive. 27:12 (Dec. 1963) (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - The Progressive. 28:06 (June 1964) (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - The Progressive. 29:12 (Dec. 1965) (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - The Progressive. 31:02 (Feb. 1967) (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - The Progressive. 32:04 (April 1968) (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Puerto del Sol. (1988). (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Pulpsmith. 4:2 (1984). (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Quarterly Review of Literature. 34 (1995). (Box 6, Folder 229a)
  - Rag Mag. 12:2 (Spring 1995). (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - The Redneck Review of Literature. (Spring 1993). (Box 7, Folder 231)
  - The Reporter. 34:02 (January 27, 1966). (Box 7, Folder 232)
  - The Reporter. 36:08 (April 20, 1967). (Box 7, Folder 233)
  - The Reporter. 36:11 (June 1, 1967). (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - The Reporter. Rhododendron (Summer 1988). (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - The Reporter. River Styx. 6 (1980). (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - The Reporter. Salon: A Journal of Aesthetics. 25 (1997). (Box 7, Folder 237)
  - The Reporter. Scree. 19,20,21 (1981). (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - The Reporter. Seneca Review. 11:2 (1981). (Box 7, Folder 239)
  - The Reporter. Shearsman. 27 (1996). (Box 7, Folder 240)
  - The Reporter. Sipapu. 22:2/44 (Fall 1992). (Box 7, Folder 241)
  - The Reporter. Slut Mag. (1991). (Box 7, Folder 242)
  - The Reporter. The Small Pond Magazine of Literature. 22:2 (1985). (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - The Reporter. Smeltmoney (n. d. ), undated (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - The Reporter. South Carolina Review. 26:1 (Fall 1993). (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - The Reporter. Southwest Review. (Spring 1991). (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - The Reporter. Spindrift. 16 (Seattle: Shoreline Community College) 1978 (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - The Reporter. The Spirit That Moves Us Reader. Seventh Anniversary Anthology. Ed. Morty Sklar. 6:2,3 (1982). (Box 7, Folder 247a)
  - The Reporter. Split City. 2 (Fall 1992). (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - The Reporter. Stations. 3,4 (1976). (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - The Reporter. Story Quarterly. 2,3 (1976). (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - The Reporter. Sun & Moon. 2 (1978). (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - The Reporter. TF Press. (Summer 1978). (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - The Reporter. Talus and Scree. 2 (Mar. 1997). (Box 7, Folder 252a)
  - The Reporter. Temporary Culture. 6 (1991). (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - The Reporter. Les Temps Modernes. 239 (1966). (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - The Reporter. Thirst. 2 (1981). (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - The Reporter. Throw Small Bullets. 2 (Fall 1993). (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Tight. 2:03, undated (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - Tight. 4:03, undated (Box 7, Folder 258)
  - Tin Wreath. 27 (1993). (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - Toledo Poets Center. 4:2 (1992). (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Total Abandon. 7, undated (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Truly Fine Press. 3 (Summer 1978). (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Tugboat. 3 (1976). (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Turning Wheel: Journal of Buddhist Peace Fellowship. (Winter 1994). (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - 2 AM Magazine. 15:1 (1991). (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - Typewriter. 5 (1974) (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - Typewriter. 8 (1978) (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Unmuzzled Ox. 14 (1996-97)., 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - Us: A Paperback Magazine. (June 1969). (Box 7, Folder 268a)
  - Videation. 1 (1977). (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - The Vincent Brothers Review. 14, undated (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - Visible Language. 11:02 (1977). (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - Visible Language. 30:03 (1996). (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Waluna: The Soho Review. 1 (1976). (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - Washington Review. 3:03 (1977). (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - Washington Review. 3:06 (1978). (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Washington Review. 18:06 (1993). (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - The Westbere Review Vol. 2, no. 3 (1979). (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - White Walls. 1 (1978). (Box 7, Folder 278)
  - White Walls. 3 (1979). (Box 7, Folder 279)
  - Woodrose. 3 (1980). (Box 7, Folder 280)
  - World. 8:3 (1974). (Box 7, Folder 281)
  - Worm. 3 (May 1992). (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - Writers' Forum. 18 (1992). (Box 7, Folder 283)
  - X: a journal of the arts. 1 (Summer 1977). (Box 7, Folder 284)
  - X: a journal of the arts. 4 (Summer 1978). (Box 7, Folder 285)
  - Xenophilia. 5 (1992). (Box 7, Folder 286)
  - Xib. 4 (Dec. 1992). (Box 7, Folder 287)
  - Yefief. 1 (Spring 1994). (Box 7, Folder 288)
  - Zahir. 2:3 (1977). (Box 7, Folder 289)
- Series III: Reviews of Works By Richard Kostelanetz
  - Contact. 4:3 (Jan. /Feb. 1964). (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Midstream. 3 (1963). (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Saturday Review. (Jan. 22, 1972). (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - The University Bookman. 15:4 (1975). (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Series IV: Articles and Books About Richard Kostelanetz
  - American Poetry and Poets of Four Centuries Olomuoc: 1976 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Delo 21:03 (1975). (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Ecci Kosti: Published Ecomia, 1967-1995. New York: Archae, 1996, 1967-1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Meat Epoch. 21 (Sept. 1997). (Box 8, Folder 3a)
  - Moral Myopia: 'The New York Review' and the New York Intellectuals. The Washington Monthly. 5:9 -1973 15-29. (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Series VI: Radio Program Listings
  - Horspiele im westdeutschen Rundfunk. 1 (Halbjahr 1981). (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Horspiele im westdeutschen Rundfunk. 2 (Halbjahr 1982). (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Horspiele im westdeutschen Rundfunk. 1 (Halbjahr 1983). (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Horspiele im westdeutschen Rundfunk. 1 (Halbjahr 1984). (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Horspiele im westdeutschen Rundfunk. 2 (Halbjahr 1984). (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Horspiele im westdeutschen Rundfunk. 2 (Halbjahr 1992). (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - In Our Time. (Jan 1981). (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Pro Musica Nova (Radio Bremen) 13-Apr Mai 1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - WBAI. 8:4,5 (April-May 1967) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - WBAI FOLIO. 8:05, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Series VII: Sound recordings
  Conditions Governing Access
  Sound recordings have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - The Aerial: A Journal in Sound 1 (Winter)., 1990 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
  - Experimental Prose. 1 audiocassette. [supplement to Sixth Assembling], undated (Box 8, Folder 2)